You have found out you have to go to court and you're going to go to court without a lawyer and your concerned about how to address the judge.
Hello, I'm Robert Todd and I'm here to answer the question how to address a judge in court.
The first thing to remember is you don't have to speak unless you're spoken to.
But, if you are spoken to and you want to address the judge you may address the judge by calling the judge Judge, Your Honor, or you may want to ask the clerk of the court that you're going to appear in how does this particular judge like to be addressed.
The clerk will provide you with that information.
Also remember, always be polite when addressing the judge.
Always stand up when addressing the judge and when your standing up let your arms flow naturally to your side as opposed to waiving your hands around and talking in an animated fashion.
Remember to be polite and always remember to make eye contact with the judge so the judge knows that you're speaking to him or her.
That's how you address a judge in court.
I'm Robert Todd and thank you for watching.